digitalcashpalace.com 2015-03-16

# Terms & Conditions - Forex Brokers Portal

#### Disclaimer

U.S. Government Required Disclaimer, quoted:

> Commodity Futures Trading Commission Futures, Currency and Options trading has large potential rewards, but also large potential risk. You must be aware of the risks and be willing to accept them in order to invest in the futures and options markets. Don’t trade with money you can’t afford to lose. This is neither a solicitation nor an offer to Buy/Sell futures or options. No representation is being made that any account will or is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those discussed on this web site. The past performance of any trading system or methodology is not necessarily indicative of future results.

Advertising disclaimer:

Banners and Featured Brokers are for advertising only. We do not recommend any brokers and will not be responsibility for any loss you may have while trading with the brokers.

#### Privacy Policy

**Personal data**

We don’t store or collect personal information about visitors. You can submit your email address upon commenting on the site but it is not required. We collect email address of those who contact us via email, contact form, commenters who decide to leave email address.

**Cookies**

We don’t use cookies to gather any information. All cookies are used to gather users’ activity on the site and we have no access to it.

**Confidentially**

All personal data we may collect are stored on our server and will be treated confidentially which necessary security to prevent any unlawful to the access the data.

**Rights of access**

Visitors can request for information about them that being collected on the site by submit request via contact form. All requests will be dealt in a proper manner.

**Link to other websites**

The privacy policy applies only to this web site. We may provide link to other web site but for reference and convenience only. We can not guarantee for its standard or be responsible for its content.

**Ad services**

We place ads on the site and may use third-party to serve the ads. These third-party companies may collect information about your visits to provide advertisers about site’s statics.

**Updates to this policy**

We reserve the right to update this policy in other to adapt it to new legal requirements. Should we do any changes we will immediately post the changes on this page.

#### Terms and Conditions

**1\. Use of the site**

DigitalCashPalace.Com is a free resource about [Forex Brokers](https://www.digitalcashpalace.com/forex-brokers-comparison/ "Forex Brokers") with information about Brokers and service that brokers provide, [Forex Bonus](https://www.digitalcashpalace.com/forex-bonus/ "Forex Bonus"), [Forex contests](https://www.digitalcashpalace.com/forex-contest/ "Forex Contests"), Press, includes [Forex forum](https://www.digitalcashpalace.com/forum/ "Forex Forum"). Information and users reviews are for information reference only.

**2\. Liability**

DigitalCashPalace.Com will accept no liability or responsibility for any actions caused by using information found on this website, including damages or losses.

**3\. Display of the information**

All Forex brokers and other companies who offer Forex trading services mentioned on DigitalCashPalace.com are for informational reference only. All information, reviews, ratings found on the site about above mentioned companies is provided according base on the company website, and/or communication with company’s representatives.

**4\. Accuracy of the information**

DigitalCashPalace.Com is updated on the daily basis but trading conditions and services for each broker may change any time. Therefore, the resource at the moment of visiting may not accuracy. DigitalCashPalace.com always try its best to stay in touch with the latest changes from brokers with help from website visitors and broker’s representatives.
